Hey, honey. How are you? What's going on? That was lunch. It was awesome. Yeah. Yeah, the girls got crazy today.
Yeah. I might have gotten a little crazy, too, but we won't talk about that. Yeah. They have a liquid lunch.
Usually. Yeah. You girls are. You went to one of those one time, remember? You had a blast, right? Yeah.
Hangin' out with us old ladies? I did. Gotta hold you guys back, though.
You can't drink as much as us. Probably not.
You should have seen Tracy dancing. Like no one else was dancing, just her.
That's pretty exciting. What's wrong?
Oh, shoulders always do. This is what I do for work now, Mom. Honey. Yeah, you're super tight. You gonna let me give you a massage yet?
You don't need to give me a massage. That's my job. That's what I'm doing. I know it's your job. I have a table set up in bags still, right now.
Yeah, but you make money doing that. Yeah, and you're my mom. I can give you a massage for free. You want me to pay me?
A little uncomfortable, you know? Why? Because it's just a little weird.
It's not easy. Just let me give you a massage. You're gonna feel so much better afterwards. It's not weird.
I mean, alright, I'll do it, but I can't get naked and stuff.
You learned. You have a sheet. I do this for a quick. It's my job now. It's not weird. You have a sheet. It's not a big deal.
Can I just keep my shorts on? I mean, not really. It's just, you're gonna be covered up. Trust me, it's fine.
If I let you do it, you'll stop bothering me about it? Yes. You need one. You're gonna be thanking me after we do it.
You're gonna be asking me for one every other day and I'll cut you back to two weeks. Just let me do it. Come on.
Alright. Where do we go?
See, I told you.
Okay. I'm proud of you. You've got it all done up and stuff.
Yeah, I moved the furniture all the way in.
This is nice.
I told you.
You're like professional and stuff.
Yeah.
Alright.
Here.
So what do I do?
Okay.
That's your sheet.
Yeah.
I mean, you just change right in there.
Right.
Yeah, everything, mom.
And that's when you have the sheet.
It's not weird.
I'm not. I'm just gonna wait for you to relax.
I'm gonna peek.
So just like put this all the way around?
Yeah.
Just relax.
Don't worry. I'm gonna help you relax.
Yeah.
Jump on the table.
So is this like bad if I'm getting a massage like after I've had wine and stuff?
No, that should probably help a little bit.
Right.
Now what?
Okay.
Jump on the table.
Where?
Like head facing that way.
It's not rocket science.
Come on.
Stop making fun of me.
I'm not.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It's not easy for me to do, you know.
I was playing tennis the other day.
I don't know what it did to my shoulder and my arm.
How much wine did you have?
Just messing with you.
It's okay.
Just supposed to be a relaxing thing.
Yes.
Do you keep busy?
How many clients do you see in here?
As I can.
About two a day at least.
Sometimes more than that.
You know, you're gonna like undo this like rep or anything?
Yeah.
Yeah, just have it.
Honey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax, relax.
Just got a tail.
Okay, so it does feel pretty good.
What's that you're using?
I just don't know.
Don't see what I haven't.
You let me do this before?
Because your friend might see your butt.
Because it's weird.
It's not weird.
I don't see what I want to wear you out, honey.
What did you do for a living?
What did you say?
Make your money.
I don't like doing that.
Your legs too, okay?
They're always sore.
Do you do those too?
I do.
How many times do you think you've told me that so far?
I don't know.
What?
Are you saying I'm bad at relaxing?
I'm just saying, wait, yeah.
All right, all right.
Relax.
Am I relaxing better now?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's still coming up, relax.
What's the matter, honey?
It stopped.
Just close your eyes.
I don't know.
It feels good, right?
Yeah, pretty good at this.
It's sore right there.
Yeah.
Is that what you're supposed to massage?
I'm just kidding.
You are?
I'm probably.
Is this the way you touch all your clients?